(Penny:)Oh, no, no, no. Crystals don't work.
Really? That's the line?
(Leonard:)Psychics are real,
but crystals are voodoo?
(Penny:)Oh, voodoo's real.
You don't wanna mess with voodoo.
(Martha:)Flatland is more
than just a mathematical essay.
(Martha:)It is also a treatise
on Victorian social mores.
(Raj:)You know,
I had never considered that.
Wow. I mean, that's going
to completely change my visits there.
[LAUGHS]
(Sheldon:)-Well, it's late.
-Uh-huh.
(Sheldon:)Time for bed.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Good night, puny human.
(Martha:)Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Yes?
(Martha:)Listen, they're kind of getting busy
in the living room...
(Martha:)...and I was wondering
if I could hang out in here for a while.
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose. Come in.
(Sheldon:)I'll sleep in Leonard's room.
Good night.